this segment is not so much a a lecture
这部分不是一场演讲
as a metal lecture or a if you wish a
作为金属演讲或如果您希望
teaser when one speaks about optioned
当一个人谈论选择时的预告片
the theory is so rich that it's very
理论是如此丰富，以至于
easy to speak about one-sided single
简单讲单面
good options and spend a lot of time on
不错的选择，花很多时间在
it but one shouldn't forget that there
它，但不要忘了那里
are other types of auctions are very
其他类型的拍卖
interesting and I just want to alert you
有趣，我只想提醒您
here two examples of such auctions so
这里有两个这样的拍卖例子
let's start with a the multiple units
让我们从多个单元开始
version of auctions so imagine that I
版本的拍卖，让我想像一下
have not one widget to sell but ten
没有一个要出售的小部件，而是十个
widgets maybe I have 10 cameras for sale
小部件，也许我有10台待售的相机
and I put them on and imagine for
我穿上它们，然后想象
example a sealed bid auction what would
例如一个密封的投标拍卖会
the bidding rules look here
竞标规则请看这里
you no longer specify only a price you
您不再只指定价格
need to specify something else for
需要指定其他内容
example a price and a quantity and so if
例如价格和数量，如果
we specify price and a quantity you
我们指定价格和数量
might say I want three cameras and I'll
可能会说我要三个相机，我会
pay you a hundred dollars for three but
付给你三百美元
maybe you'd be happy to get also four
也许你会很高兴得到四个
cameras for the right price for example
例如价格合适的相机
if I gave you're willing to pay a
如果我给你愿意支付
hundred price $100 for three cameras
一百个价格$ 100三个相机
perhaps you'd be happy to get four
也许你会很高兴得到四个
cameras for hundred and ten dollars
一百美元的相机
certainly for a hundred dollars you'd be
当然只要一百美元，
happy to get four and and three cameras
很高兴得到四个和三个相机
or is it the case and so one needs to
还是这样，所以需要
specify these more complicated rules
指定这些更复杂的规则
here in general the most general way to
一般而言，这是最一般的方式
specify things in a sealed bid auction
在密封的投标拍卖中指定事物
would be to specify is what's called a
将指定什么是所谓的
schedule somewhat non-standard use of
安排一些非标准的使用
the term but it's a whole curve that
这个词，但这是一条完整的曲线
says for each price how much am I
说每个价格我多少钱
willing to how many units am I willing
我愿意多少单位
to buy for that price
以该价格购买
and presumably and this is not universal
大概这不是普遍的
but you might have a monotonicity rule
但您可能会有单调性规则
so that is the higher the price the
所以价格越高
smaller the number of units I might want
我可能想要的单位数少
to buy one can definitely find counter
买一个绝对可以找到柜台
examples to this but that would be a
例子，但这将是
natural restriction in certain cases
在某些情况下自然限制
think now about a an open outcry auction
现在考虑公开喊价拍卖
so for example think about the Japanese
例如以日本人为例
auction in let me recall what it is the
拍卖让我想起这是什么
Japanese auction there is an ascending
日本拍卖呈上升趋势
price called out by the auctioneer and
拍卖师要求的价格，以及
people in the single unit good in the
单一单位中的人在
single unit case people start by all
单位案例的人从头开始
being in so who will buy who will buy
在谁会买谁会买
this camera for zero dollars everybody's
这台相机零美元大家的
in and as the price rises one by one the
随着价格一一上涨
bidders sit down irrevocably and when
竞标者无可挽回地坐下，何时
there's only one person the standing
站着只有一个人
they get the camera for that price what
他们以那个价格得到相机
happens when I have now ten cameras for
当我现在有十个摄像机用于
sale what would be the natural
出售自然是什么
generalization of the Japanese auction
日本拍卖的概括
well here's a one natural generalization
好，这是一个自然的概括
and it is specifying a quantity so I
它指定了数量，所以我
have ten cameras for sale and I ask how
有十台相机要出售，我问如何
many do you want at zero dollars well
您想以零美元买到很多吗
presumably you want all ten and as the
想必您想全部十个
price rises you reduce your demand until
价格上涨，您减少需求直到
and whenever you reduces you can never
无论何时减少，您都永远无法
bring it back up again if it ever goes
如果有的话，再次备份
down to zero then you're totally out of
降到零，那么你完全没钱了
the game and when does the auction stop
游戏以及何时停止拍卖
well as soon as the demand is is is less
需求少就好
than supply you stop so when the total
比供应停止，所以当总
demand by the agent at a given point is
代理商在给定时间点的需求是
less than ten will stop the auction that
少于十个将停止拍卖
raises an interesting question what
提出了一个有趣的问题
happens if in a discrete case when
如果在离散情况下
suddenly we went from a demand of 11
突然我们从11的需求
of eight we stop the auction what do we
在八分之一的拍卖中我们停止拍卖
do the two extra cameras well there's
做好两个额外的相机
interesting topic for discussion that
有趣的讨论话题
illustrates some of the subtleties that
说明了一些微妙之处
come up when we go from single unit to
当我们从单个单元转到
multiple unit a different class of
多个单元，不同类别的
auctions are special because they're
拍卖很特别，因为它们
motivated by specific applications and
由特定的应用程序和
ad options or advertising auctions are a
广告选项或广告竞标是
good example so we all have the
很好的例子，所以我们都有
experience of going to an online site
进入在线网站的经验
most famously Google and doing for
最著名的是Google，
example a search gathered getting our
例如，搜集到的搜索使我们
search results
搜索结果
hopefully accurately reflecting the
希望准确反映
relevance of the site's to us but then
该网站与我们的相关性，然后
on the right we have these sponsored
在右边，我们有这些赞助
links and these are links that
链接，这些是链接
advertisers paid to give to us and the
广告客户付费给我们和
typically tied to the search term that
通常与搜索字词相关联，
we have so for example if we tie if we
例如，如果我们并列，
type in Paris hotels then there are
键入巴黎酒店，然后有
advertisers out there who paid for the
在那里付费的广告客户
right to display us their advertising
向我们展示其广告的权利
when we type in those terms and so how
当我们输入这些术语时，如何
does one run an auction for such search
有没有人为这种搜索进行拍卖
terms knowing that they are run millions
知道他们已经运行了数百万条的术语
of times throughout the day all over the
整天的时间
world and they are run in different
世界，他们在不同的地方
places multiple times and so wanting to
放置多次，所以想
design an auction that is appropriate
设计合适的拍卖
for this particular application so
对于这个特殊的应用
sponsored search auctions or ad auctions
赞助的搜索拍卖或广告拍卖
are a very rich topic of research in
是一个非常丰富的研究主题
both academia and industry finally let
学术界和工业界终于让
me speak briefly about combinatorial
我简要谈一下组合
auctions those are very interesting both
拍卖都非常有趣
because they are commercially very
因为它们在商业上非常
relevant and because they give rise to a
相关的，因为它们引起了
host of very interesting intellectual
非常有趣的知识分子的主人
issues so what's an example of
问题，这是什么例子
combinatorial auction imagine an auction
组合拍卖想象拍卖
for shoes you could have an auction for
对于鞋子，您可以进行拍卖
left shoes and you couldn't have an
左鞋，你不能
auction for right shoes but that'd be
拍卖合适的鞋子，但那会是
very weird because you really don't have
非常奇怪，因为您真的没有
a use for only left or only a right shoe
仅用于左鞋或仅用于右鞋
and so well you really would want to be
好吧，你真的很想成为
able to bid for both of those together
能够一起竞标
this seems frivolous but now think about
这似乎很轻浮，但现在考虑一下
a popular consumer auction sites such as
受欢迎的消费者拍卖网站，例如
eBay maybe you want to put together a
易趣也许你想把一个
home theater system so you need a
家庭影院系统，因此您需要一个
television you need a DVD player and
电视，您需要DVD播放器和
maybe you need some other items that go
也许您还需要其他一些物品
along to make a home entertainment
进行家庭娱乐
system well you go out there and you bid
系统很好，你去那里，你竞标
for televisions first off you have many
首先要看电视你有很多
different televisions to bid on many
不同的电视竞标很多
different televisions are very same
不同的电视都一样
model and even more so of different
型号甚至更多
models
楷模
you only need one television so here you
你只需要一台电视，所以在这里你
are you have these two televisions that
你有这两台电视吗
you're bidding on but you don't want to
您正在竞标，但您不想
get both of them so how can you bid on
都拿到，所以你怎么出价
and make sure you get the tail of the
并确保您了解
television you prefer but only one at
您喜欢的电视，但只有一部
the same time perhaps you have here a
同时也许你在这里
DVD player that you're bidding on but
您竞标的DVD播放器，但
you really wouldn't want to get the DVD
你真的不想拿DVD
player alone a DVD without a television
单独播放DVD而不播放电视
to display it on would be completely
在上面显示
valueless to you and yet these are
对你毫无价值，但这些都是
different options and so what you have
不同的选择，所以你有什么
here are examples of are called
这是被称为的例子
complementarity and substitutability the
互补性和可替代性
two TVs you may be looking at our
两台电视，您可能正在看我们的
substitute it doesn't mean that one is
替代它并不意味着一个是
completely equivalent to the other but
完全等同于另一个，但
it means that that the value of both of
这意味着两者的价值
them together to you is much less that
他们在一起给你要少得多
the some are their individual value to
一些是他们的个人价值
you in the extreme case is simply the
在极端情况下，你就是
value of the maximum maximum among the
其中最大最大值的值
two on the other hand the connection
另一方面，两个连接
between
之间
in the DVD player and the television is
在DVD播放器和电视中
that of complementarity the value of the
互补的价值
DVD player plus the television is much
DVD播放器加电视很多
more than the value of the DVD player
超过DVD播放机的价值
alone plus the value of the TV alone
加上电视的价值
because the value of the DVD alone is
因为仅DVD的价值就是
zero to you and so that's those two
零给你，那就是那两个
goods are complementary there are many
商品互补有很多
examples of combinatorial auctions and
组合拍卖和
most famous example are the spectrum
最著名的例子是频谱
auction you can you think of the
拍卖您可以想到
spectrum auction these are rights for
频谱拍卖这些是权利
you to use the electromagnetic spectrum
您使用电磁频谱
and you can think of those as a matrix
您可以将它们视为矩阵
where the rows are their regions in
行在其中的区域
question for example geographical
例如地理问题
regions in the US and the columns are
美国的地区和列
certain bandwidth in megahertz for say
一定的兆赫带宽
that are being auctions you could have a
正在拍卖中，您可能会有
handful say five different bands that
少数说五个不同的乐队
are auctions and many hundreds of
是拍卖会，还有数百个
regions and so each cell in this matrix
区域，因此此矩阵中的每个单元格
is a good but you have very strong
很好，但是你很坚强
complementarity among the rows and very
行之间的互补性
strong substitutability among the
强大的替代性
columns the columns are really
列是真的
interchangeable only needs one bandwidth
可互换只需要一个带宽
and you don't care which it is on the
而且你不在乎它在哪
other hand if you're a setted or
另一方面，如果您是固定的，或者
operator for example getting a whole
运算符，例如得到一个整体
contiguous segments is something you
连续的段是你的事
essentially need in order to run a
基本上需要运行
service you don't want to get just a
您不想得到的服务
little pocket here a little pocket there
这里的小口袋这里的小口袋
and so you really need say all the
所以你真的需要说所有
metropolitan areas or all of the Midwest
大都市地区或整个中西部
in order to justify rolling out a
为了证明推出一个
service there that's an example of where
服务那里是一个例子
combinatorial auction would be very
组合拍卖会非常
natural
自然
interestingly it hasn't really run this
有趣的是，它并没有真正运行
way although the discussions about
方式虽然讨论
running it's quite quite as a
运行它相当
combinatorial auctions commit to options
组合拍卖承诺期权
give rise to many issues how to design
引起很多问题如何设计
the auction to ensure the right economic
拍卖以确保正确的经济
properties there are interesting
那里的属性很有趣
computational issues so find finding the
计算问题，所以找到
winner in a simple English auction or in
简单的英语拍卖或
a sealed bid auction is trivial you look
密封的竞价拍卖看起来微不足道
at the maximum among a set of numbers
在一组数字中最大
computing the outcome of a combinatorial
计算组合的结果
auction is distinctly more complicated
拍卖显然要复杂得多
both competing who the winner is and in
既竞争获胜者又是谁
particular computing the payments can be
特别是计算付款可以是
very complicated in the in the technical
在技​​术上非常复杂
language the this so-called winner
语言这个所谓的赢家
determination problem is what's called
确定问题就是所谓的
np-complete which means that it's a a an
np-complete这意味着它是一个
agreed upon difficult problem to compute
同意计算困难的问题
and there's been a literature about how
并且有关于如何
to do it in a practical manner
以实际的方式做到这一点
nonetheless so these are examples of non
尽管如此，这些都是非
non simple actions multiple-unit
非简单动作多单元
sponsored search options compare toriel
赞助商搜索选项比较
auctions and all this by way of working
拍卖和所有这些通过工作
your appetite to learn more about these
您的胃口以了解更多有关这些的信息
kinds of auctions
各种拍卖